const data = [
  {
    question: "Abase",
    options: {
      a: "Humiliate",
      b: "Anger",
      c: "Defy",
      d: "Spend"
    },
    correct: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Abjure",
    options: {
      a: "Sanctify",
      b: "Pitiful",
      c: "Renounce",
      d: "Abolish"
    },
    correct: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "Atrophy",
    options: {
      a: "Victimize",
      b: "Decay",
      c: "Resist",
      d: "To reward"
    },
    correct: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Bourgeoies",
    options: {
      a: "French Victory Ritual",
      b: "King",
      c: "Peasant",
      d: "Capitalist"
    },
    correct: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "Cacophany",
    options: {
      a: "Opera",
      b: "Disharmonious Sound",
      c: "Pleasant sound pleasing the ego",
      d: "Account Book"
    },
    correct: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Clandestine",
    options: {
      a: "Luxurious",
      b: "Secret",
      c: "Merciful",
      d: "Priest"
    },
    correct: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Coagulate",
    options: {
      a: "Clot",
      b: "Sing Together",
      c: "Rebel",
      d: "Thin"
    },
    correct: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Consecrate",
    options: {
      a: "Destroy",
      b: "Dedicate",
      c: "Antagonize",
      d: "Meditate"
    },
    correct: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Deleterious",
    options: {
      a: "Chaotic",
      b: "Harmful",
      c: "Diplomatic",
      d: "Spendthrift"
    },
    correct: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Garrulous",
    options: {
      a: "Wordy",
      b: "Wild",
      c: "Stubborn",
      d: "Dangerous"
    },
    correct: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Hegemony",
    options: {
      a: "Plagiarisim",
      b: "Obdurate",
      c: "Organizing",
      d: "Domination"
    },
    correct: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "Ignominious",
    options: {
      a: "Ill omened",
      b: "Poor",
      c: "Humiliating",
      d: "Ignorant"
    },
    correct: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "Maudlin",
    options: {
      a: "Weakly Sentimental",
      b: "Overly Aggressive",
      c: "Extremely Interesting",
      d: "Fiercely Independent"
    },
    correct: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Obstreperous",
    options: {
      a: "Noisy",
      b: "Stubborn",
      c: "Resilient",
      d: "Jealous"
    },
    correct: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Perfunctory",
    options: {
      a: "Smell",
      b: "Persisting",
      c: "No Enthusiasm",
      d: "Mundane"
    },
    correct: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "Sagacity",
    options: {
      a: "Shrewdness",
      b: "Stinginess",
      c: "Ignorance",
      d: "Fiercely Independent"
    },
    correct: "a"
  }
];
